1a. I chose this dataset because I think its interesting to examine people's varying dietary choices and I thought it would be interesting to do so with college students.
1b. The data was collected from a sample of college students from Mercyhurst University which 126 of them responded to.
1c. A question I examined further was question 2, the coffee preferences of female students.

2a. Specific pieces of information that needed to be extracted from the data set were the GPAs of the respondees, their coffee preferences and gender.
2b. My biggest difficulty was that the dataset I downloaded showed up in a different language when I put it into vscode. I instead coded by looking at the preview in kaggle to figure it out. Another difficulty I encountered was processing the GPAs, which I processed as a string rather than a double.

3a. A takeaway is that female students prefer espresso over creamy frapuccino.
3b. One limitation is that I did not know the total amount of people sampled. I only knew the amount of respondees, which is 126. It would be beneficial to know the total people sampled to draw more precise conclusions.
3c. Something else I wouldve implemented is compraing male respondee's coffee preferences to their female counterparts.